<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>

    <plugin id="com.zps.Zest" url="https://zest-internal.zingplay.com/static/release/latest/Zest-latest.zip" version="1.9.898">
        <idea-version since-build="223.0" until-build="259.*"/>
        <name>Zest</name>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Zest: Smarter Java Development with AI</h2>
            <p><b>Zest</b> supercharges your IntelliJ workflow. Instantly generate JUnit tests, implement TODOs, and refactor for testability—all powered by AI.</p>
        ]]></description>
        <change-notes><![CDATA[
            <h3>Version 1.9.898 - Smart JSON Parsing & Code Health Resilience 🛡️</h3>
            <h4>🧠 Smart JSON Parsing</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>JsonParsingHelper Added</b> - New utility class with multiple fallback strategies for handling malformed LLM responses</li>
                <li><b>Resilient Parsing</b> - Gracefully handles JSON with missing commas, unclosed brackets, and embedded code blocks</li>
                <li><b>Partial Results Preserved</b> - Code Health analysis now displays whatever it can parse, even from broken JSON</li>
                <li><b>Better Error Recovery</b> - Multiple parsing attempts with different strategies ensure maximum data extraction</li>
            </ul>

            <h4>💪 Code Health Improvements</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Partial Analysis Support</b> - Code Health now stores and displays results even when parsing partially fails</li>
                <li><b>Issue Prioritization</b> - Shows only the most critical issues (max 5 per file) for better focus</li>
                <li><b>Storage Reliability</b> - Fixed issue where partial analysis results weren't being stored properly</li>
                <li><b>Better Notifications</b> - Replaced blocking dialogs with non-intrusive notifications</li>
            </ul>

            <h4>🎯 Completion System Simplification</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Removed Overlap Detection</b> - Eliminated complex overlap detection logic for more predictable completions</li>
                <li><b>Stable Suggestions</b> - Code suggestions are now more consistent and reliable</li>
                <li><b>Code Cleanup</b> - Removed ~400 lines of unnecessary overlap detector code</li>
                <li><b>Better Performance</b> - Simpler logic means faster completion processing</li>
            </ul>

            <h4>🧹 Code Quality</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Method Refactoring</b> - All methods now under 20 lines for better maintainability</li>
                <li><b>Cleaner Architecture</b> - Simplified completion and Code Health systems</li>
                <li><b>Better Separation</b> - JSON parsing logic centralized in JsonParsingHelper</li>
                <li><b>Improved Testing</b> - More focused unit tests for critical components</li>
            </ul>

            <p><em>This release makes Zest more resilient when dealing with unpredictable LLM responses while simplifying core systems for better reliability. 🚀</em></p>
        ]]></change-notes>
        <vendor>Zingplay Game Studio</vendor>
    </plugin>

</plugins>