<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>

    <plugin id="com.zps.Zest" url="https://zest-internal.zingplay.com/static/release/latest/Zest-latest.zip" version="1.9.895">
        <idea-version since-build="223.0" until-build="259.*"/>
        <name>Zest</name>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Zest: Smarter Java Development with AI</h2>
            <p><b>Zest</b> supercharges your IntelliJ workflow. Instantly generate JUnit tests, implement TODOs, and refactor for testability—all powered by AI.</p>
        ]]></description>
        <change-notes><![CDATA[
            <h3>Version 1.9.895 - RAG Removal & Inline Completion Performance Boost 🚀</h3>
            <h4>⚡ Major Performance Improvements</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>RAG System Removed</b> - Eliminated 50-200ms latency from inline completions by removing RAG (Retrieval Augmented Generation)</li>
                <li><b>Faster Context Collection</b> - Inline completions now rely purely on PSI-based analysis and direct code relationships</li>
                <li><b>Reduced Memory Usage</b> - Removed RAG chunk caching and embedding computation overhead</li>
                <li><b>Simplified Pipeline</b> - Cleaner, more reliable completion system with fewer failure points</li>
                <li><b>Better Responsiveness</b> - Eliminated async RAG retrieval complexity from completion flow</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h4>🧹 Code Quality Improvements</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Removed Files</b> - Deleted InlineCompletionRAG.java and cleaned up all RAG dependencies</li>
                <li><b>Updated Context Collectors</b> - ZestLeanContextCollectorPSI no longer includes RAG chunks or retrieval</li>
                <li><b>Streamlined Caching</b> - LeanContextCache simplified by removing RAG-specific caching logic</li>
                <li><b>Cleaner Prompts</b> - Prompt builders no longer include RAG context sections</li>
                <li><b>Simplified Services</b> - PreemptiveAsyncAnalyzerService and Quick Actions no longer use RAG</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h4>🎯 What You Get</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Instant Completions</b> - Sub-millisecond inline completion context retrieval</li>
                <li><b>More Reliable</b> - Fewer dependencies and potential failure points</li>
                <li><b>Better Resource Usage</b> - Lower CPU and memory consumption</li>
                <li><b>Cleaner Codebase</b> - Removed ~2000+ lines of RAG-related code</li>
            </ul>
            
            <p><em>This release dramatically improves inline completion performance by removing the RAG bottleneck while maintaining all core functionality through PSI analysis and code relationships. 🚀</em></p>
        ]]></change-notes>
        <vendor>Zingplay Game Studio</vendor>
    </plugin>

</plugins>