<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<plugins>

    <plugin id="com.zps.Zest" url="https://zest-internal.zingplay.com/static/release/latest/Zest-latest.zip" version="1.9.894">
        <idea-version since-build="223.0" until-build="259.*"/>
        <name>Zest</name>
        <description><![CDATA[
            <h2>Zest: Smarter Java Development with AI</h2>
            <p><b>Zest</b> supercharges your IntelliJ workflow. Instantly generate JUnit tests, implement TODOs, and refactor for testability—all powered by AI.</p>
        ]]></description>
        <change-notes><![CDATA[
            <h3>Version 1.9.894 - Context Collector Performance Optimization ⚡</h3>
            <h4>⚡ Context Collector Performance</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Configurable Blocking Delays</b> - Added settings to disable or minimize all blocking delays in context collection</li>
                <li><b>Non-Blocking Priority</b> - Enhanced context collection to prioritize cached, non-blocking approaches</li>
                <li><b>Performance Settings</b> - New configuration options: disableContextCollectorBlocking and minimizeContextCollectorDelays</li>
                <li><b>Optimized Background Processing</b> - All delay timers now respect performance configuration (1ms minimum or disabled)</li>
                <li><b>Reduced Async Analysis Overhead</b> - Expensive async analysis is skipped when blocking is disabled</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h4>🔧 Configuration Improvements</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>ZestGlobalSettings Enhanced</b> - Added two new boolean settings for context collector performance control</li>
                <li><b>ConfigurationManager Extended</b> - New getter/setter methods with proper null safety and logging</li>
                <li><b>ZestBackgroundContextManager Optimized</b> - All hardcoded delays replaced with configurable helper methods</li>
                <li><b>Context Collection Flow</b> - Enhanced to respect blocking configuration and prefer cached data</li>
            </ul>
            
            <h4>🚀 Performance Benefits</h4>
            <ul>
                <li><b>Near-Instant Context</b> - Context collection can now operate with minimal delays (1ms) or no blocking at all</li>
                <li><b>Responsive UI</b> - Significantly improved plugin responsiveness during code completion and analysis</li>
                <li><b>Smart Caching</b> - Better utilization of cached VCS and file context without unnecessary waits</li>
                <li><b>Configurable Trade-offs</b> - Users can choose between performance and comprehensive context collection</li>
            </ul>
            
            <p><em>Major performance optimization that makes the context collector nearly instant while maintaining functionality. ⚡</em></p>
        ]]></change-notes>
        <vendor>Zingplay Game Studio</vendor>
    </plugin>

</plugins>